KENNETH MARK COFFIE

28 Cascade Road, Liverpool, L24 9LH | 07484680764 | markcoffiekenneth@gmail.com | kennymark.co

Objective

A highly motivated Computer Science student with a deep interest in technology and business as well as a moderate level of experience in website development. Consistently working to the highest professional standards drawing on experience and a wide range of technical expertise. Additionally, an effective team player with excellent communication and organisational skills combined with a will to win and succeed.

Education

COMPUTER SCIENCE | 2016-2018 | UNIVERSITY OF CHESTER

 Related coursework: Systems Development, Database, Computer Systems and Network, Website Production and Programming

COMPUTING AND SYSTEMS DEVELOPMENT | 2014-2016 | CITY OF LIVERPOOL COLLEGE

 Related coursework: Data Design, IT security, Java, LAN Technologies, Data Structures and Algorithms

Skills & Abilities

MANAGEMENT

- · Managed a team that was in charge of QAA Review for the City of Liverpool College
- Project Manager for software development team that built Research Ethics Committee of the University of Chester

SALES

· Sales experience gained after working as a sales advisor for Pareto Digital Associates

COMMUNICATION

• Fluent in 6 languages and very confident speaking in public and communicating with people and teams

LEADERSHIP

• Lead developer of a software development team to build a website for Research Ethics Committee of the University of Chester

Experience

WEB DEVELOPER | UNIVERSITY OF CHESTER | MAY – JUNE 2017

· Leading the team to build a website for Research Ethics Committee for the University

SALES ADVISOR | PARETO GLOBALS ASSOCIATES | MAY - JULY 2015

- · Liaise with customers and get to know them
- Selling products to customers
- Signing up customers up for charities and packages

LEAD STUDENT REPRESENTATIVE | CITY OF LIVERPOOL | SEPTEMBER 2014 - JUNE 2016

- · Schedule meeting to talk about student issues
- · Lead and managed the QAA review for the college

INDEPENDENT WEB PROJECTS | PARETO GLOBALS ASSOCIATES | JUNE 2012 – TILL DATE

- This is the place for a brief summary of your key responsibilities and most stellar accomplishments.
- · Developed web design skills
- · Worked with APIs

Computer skills

- Web programming in HTML, CSS, JavaScript/jQuery, MySQL/MongoDB and ASP.NET, NodeJS, Meteor, VueJs etc.
- Programing and development in Java, C++, C#.
- · Some experience of Node.js, Meteor and
- · NetBeans and Eclipse IDEs for Java development.
- Agile software development methodologies
- · Microsoft Office.
- · Various operating systems including Windows XP/Vista/7, Mac OS X and Ubuntu.

Interests

- · Writing electronic music digitally using Digital Audio Workstations like Studio one and FL Studio.
- · Creative writing including lyrics for music I make
- · Research and gathering information for topics such politics, web development and economics